Elena | Coach: Let's start with a quick check-in. How is everyone feeling about the sprint we just closed?
David: Relieved, honestly. We shipped the payment flow but I think we took on too much and it showed in the last two days.
Priya: Agreed. We had three blockers that weren't flagged until Wednesday. I think our estimation process needs work.
Elena | Coach: What's one thing that would have made the sprint go smoother if you'd done it on day one?
David: A clearer definition of done for the payment ticket. We had three different interpretations across the team.
Priya: And earlier dependency mapping. We didn't know we were blocked on the backend team until it was already urgent.
Elena | Coach: So definition of done and dependency mapping upfront. Are those things you can add to your sprint kick-off checklist?
David: Yes, I can own creating that checklist by end of this week.
Priya: And I'll set up a short dependency review slot at the start of every sprint — thirty minutes max.
Elena | Coach: Great. Let's revisit both in two weeks and see if they made a difference. What's the team's energy level going into this next sprint?
David: Better now that we've talked. I think we just needed to name the problems out loud.
Elena | Coach: That's exactly what retrospectives are for. Good work today, both of you.